[
	{
		"question": "What are the associations between subsystems?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9991938471794128,
			"start": 0,
			"end": 5,
			"answer": "Pipes"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of a subsystem that can be shared by a different application?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9825912714004517,
			"start": 1751,
			"end": 1774,
			"answer": "Pipe and filter Filters"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What can be technical or user interface prototypes Functional Requirements Describe the functionality that the system needs, as given by the client and observed from the user?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.982234001159668,
			"start": 0,
			"end": 11,
			"answer": "Prototyping"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is one of the most known plan-driven processes?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9820718765258789,
			"start": 552,
			"end": 561,
			"answer": "Waterfall"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "Who created UML notation?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9438468217849731,
			"start": 573,
			"end": 589,
			"answer": "The Three Amigos"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "How does Client/Server Server provide services to instances of other subsystems called?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9259909987449646,
			"start": 516,
			"end": 523,
			"answer": "clients"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is synchronization possible via the pipes?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.8614257574081421,
			"start": 140,
			"end": 173,
			"answer": "Filters are executed concurrently"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the rationale behind the decisions made?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.8037554621696472,
			"start": 435,
			"end": 459,
			"answer": "Rational driven activity"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "Which subsystem can become a bottleneck?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.7419714331626892,
			"start": 1572,
			"end": 1590,
			"answer": "central repository"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is used to manage the sequence of interactions with the user?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.6271803975105286,
			"start": 1212,
			"end": 1225,
			"answer": "Storage layer"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of a class dependent on the container?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.5932823419570923,
			"start": 103,
			"end": 119,
			"answer": "abstract class A"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "How do subsystems access and modify a single data structure?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.5648881793022156,
			"start": 1464,
			"end": 1482,
			"answer": "central repository"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What does Theory Software engineering include?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.5533217787742615,
			"start": 59,
			"end": 115,
			"answer": "Modeling activity Deals with complexity through modeling"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "How does a class have one reason to change?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.5469356179237366,
			"start": 1461,
			"end": 1507,
			"answer": "Meaning a class should have one responsibility"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of a subsystem based on?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.4750354588031769,
			"start": 1598,
			"end": 1647,
			"answer": "flowcharts State Machine Diagram Behavior diagram"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the difference between iterative and incremental process planning?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.4453713297843933,
			"start": 79,
			"end": 149,
			"answer": "easier to change the process to reflect changing customer requirements"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is a problem-solving activity driven by experimentation?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.43237778544425964,
			"start": 209,
			"end": 215,
			"answer": "Search"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What does Agile processes take precedence over planning and documentation?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.3744061291217804,
			"start": 396,
			"end": 415,
			"answer": "shappable\" software"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "How does waterfall Requirement Elicitation Identifies and discovers the requirements from the client?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.3497121036052704,
			"start": 552,
			"end": 605,
			"answer": "Requirement engineering Used in a plan-driven process"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is a problem with the central repository?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.283737450838089,
			"start": 1591,
			"end": 1614,
			"answer": "can become a bottleneck"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the definition of a user's role?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.04057919979095459,
			"start": 1461,
			"end": 1507,
			"answer": "Meaning a class should have one responsibility"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.004685001447796822,
			"start": 12,
			"end": 68,
			"answer": "Iterative or incremental process planning is incremental"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.002914540469646454,
			"start": 47,
			"end": 104,
			"answer": "Each filter knows only of the data received from the pipe"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 5.519587830349337e-6,
			"start": 118,
			"end": 182,
			"answer": "models are built of the system as well as the application domain"
		}
	}
]
